{
    "subject": "resource/OrangeScape",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.orangescape.com",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of OrangeScape is http://www.orangescape.com.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9635156393051147,
            "question": "Give me the web address for OrangeScape's homepage."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.935482382774353,
            "question": "What is the URL of OrangeScape's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195412397384644,
            "question": "Provide the web address for OrangeScape."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.898436963558197,
            "question": "What is the official website of OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773312568664551,
            "question": "Where can you find OrangeScape's website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8418955206871033,
            "question": "What address is associated with OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8257452249526978,
            "question": "What is the online location of OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7912270426750183,
            "question": "How can you access OrangeScape online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7628450989723206,
            "question": "If you want to visit OrangeScape, what URL should you enter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7295194864273071,
            "question": "Where is OrangeScape located on the internet?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of OrangeScape is http://www.orangescape.com.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7100_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you want to visit OrangeScape, what URL should you enter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7100_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can you access OrangeScape online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7100_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the online location of OrangeScape?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7100_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7100_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indicate that the official website of OrangeScape Inc. is orangescape.com, which supports the homepage being http://www.orangescape.com."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}